orafaq.com 2005-12-12

# Oracle FAQ: Privacy Policy Statement

Index > About this FAQ > Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy Statement:

The Oracle FAQ respects the privacy of its visitors and participants. This statement explains our privacy and data-protection practices: 

  * Wherever we collect personal information, we will do so transparently and only with your informed consent.

  * We do not sell, trade or rent personal information.

  * We do not take part in spam advertising, nor do we support or help people doing so.

  * We cannot protect private information (like telephone numbers or E-mail addresses) left by users on message boards and chat forums. We will, however, remove such information when requested to do so.

  * **Third Party Advertising** : We use MaxOnline and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please [click here](http://www.maxonline.com/privacy_policy/index.php).

  * **Third Party Cookies** : In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.

  * We assume your consent to this policy if you continue to visit our site.

If you have any additional questions about our privacy policy, please contact our webmaster.
